LIDIYA KOCHERZHUK

Trainee Node.js developer



SUMMARY:

I am a persistent, goal-oriented, fast-learning novice Node.js developer. Although I've not had any commercial experience yet. But, I've been working hard to learn JavaScript and its technologies in the "JavaScript Complex" course by OktenSchool for the last year.

- I did my homework diligently and usually got good feedback from my mentors.
- And even got the highest score for the "MovieDB(React.js)" project developed.

Also I really value good relations in a team and always supported it in previous jobs. I hope my candidature will suit you and we will be able to create great projects together.

CONTACT



+38(068)-382-3743



lidiyakocherzchuk@gmail.com



@Lidiya_Kocherzhuk



in <u>Lidiya Kocherzhuk</u>



LidiyaKocherzhuk



Lviv, Ukraine

LANGUAGES

Ukranian: Native

• English: Intermediate

· Czech: Intermediate

EDUCATION

JavaScript Complex

OKTEN SCHOOL

September 2021 - present

Master Of Restaurant Service

IVANO-FRANKIVSK COLLEGE OF RESTAURANT SERVICE AND TOURISM

2012-2014

PET PROJECTS

Furniture shop

The project have not finished yet, but I am working on it. I used React Typescript for **Furniture shop client**. I used NodeJs (Express) for Furniture_shop_backend.

MovieDB-React.js

The project is made on the basis of the MovieDB library. I used Redux, Router-Dom, React Hooks technologies and HTML & CSS.

MovieDB-Angular

The project is made on the basis of the MovieDB library. I used Routing, Lazy-loading, HTTP client technologies and HTML & CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Car Seat Assembly Line Worker

ADIENT BOR

February 2021 - May 2021

Assistant Cook

DON GIOVANNI HOTEL PRAGUE

February 2019 - Mart 2020

TECH SKILLS:

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Angular
- MySql
- MongoDB
- Node.js (Express)
- Docker (basics)
- AWS (basics)

SOFT SKILLS:

- Attentiveness
- Reliability
- Punctuality
- Team Player